Hell Just Got A Lot Hotter!
Nightmare Sisters is a horror, comedy film directed by David DeCoteau.
Three socially awkward sorority girls invite three fraternity pledges over for a night of fun, but when the group holds a
séance, the girls find themselves possessed by a shaman who transforms them into lustful, uninhibited succubi.
Melody, played by Linnea Quigley.
Marci, played by Brinke Stevens.
Mickey (as Michelle McClellan), played by Michelle Bauer.
Phil, played by Timothy Kauffman.
J.J., played by Matthew Phelps.
Bud (as C.J. Cox), played by C. Jay Cox.
Nightmare Sisters (also released as Sorority Succubus Sisters) is a
1988 direct-to-video, low-budget, horror comedy.
It is notable as one of only two films in which 1980s scream queens Linnea Quigley, Brinke Stevens, and
Michelle Bauer appear together, excluding later reunion films such as 1313:Cougar Cult.
The film explores themes of exploitation, seduction, sorority, occult, succubus.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.